Breno Pinho

Motivated student working towards Bachelor of Applied Science and Engineering in Computer Engineering, with a Minor in Al and Machine Learning. Possess experience in Project Management, Design, and Lab work. Proven success working within fast-paced, collaborative and goal-driven settings.

WORK HISTORY

Signal Integrity Engineer, 05/2022 - 08/2023 Intel, Toronto, ON

- Handled Signal Integrity issues on over 20 different CPU and GPU based boards
- Gained proficiency with both physical measurement tools and virtual simulation tools
- Worked closely with Siemens, Cadence and Keysight tools and software
- Managed and concluded multiple projects with the goal of helping automate team workload, and increase efficiency

Mentorship Director, 03/2020 - 03/2021 University of Toronto, Toronto, ON

- Assisted 80 First-year University of Toronto students with transitioning into University of Toronto's Faculty of Engineering
- Coordinated online Mentorship events by preparing and executing organizational strategies for group allocation
- Devoted special emphasis to punctuality and worked to maintain outstanding attendance record, consistently arriving to work ready to start immediately

Project Manager, 01/2020 - 12/2020 University of Toronto, Toronto, ON

- Designed a Mapping and Path-finding Software in C++
- Developed executive presentations and reports to facilitate project evaluation and process improvement
- Managed an Engineering Team and developed a real-time pathfinding algorithm in the top 12% of over 100 teams

AWARDS

- University of Toronto Dean's List (12/2019 Present)
- Consistently held a GPA over 3.8 every year since 2019
- Current GPA: 3.91

EDUCATION

Bachelor Of Applied Science, Computer Engineering, Expected in 04/2024 University of Toronto - Toronto, ON, Canada

- Algorithms and Data Structures
- Computer Organization
- Introductory Electronics
- Programming Fundamentals
- Fields and Waves
- Artificial Intelligence Fundamentals
- Introduction to Control Systems
- Software Engineering



Toronto, ON



6476140492



breno.pinho@mail.utoronto.ca

SKILLS

- Proficiency in C/C++ and Python Programming
- Skilled in use of Java, JavaScript, HTML and VBScript
- Knowledge of AI and ML fundamentals
- Further skills with PyTorch and TensorFlow
- Knowledge of Circuit and Hardware Design
- Project Management Experience
- Event Coordination Experience
- Proficiency in various Simulation and Measurement tools